School of the Museum of Fine Arts Records UA133
Tufts Archival Research Center
- Development records, circa 1987 -- 2016; UA133.007; 12.58 Linear Feet
  - Artist slides Q-Z and artMatters photographs, circa 2000 -- 2010; UA133.007.036 (Box 36)
  - Development CDs and DVDS, circa 1990 -- 2016; UA133.007.073 (Box 73)
  - Development slides, circa 2000 -- 2001; UA133.007.041 (Box 41)
  - Event and exhibition slides, photographs and contact sheets, and artMatters photographs, 1987 -- 2005; UA133.007.037 (Box 37)
  - Events and exhibitions, student and faculty art slides, circa 1991 -- 2002; UA133.007.039 (Box 39)
  - Media coverage reports and artMatters slide submissions, 2000 -- 2012; UA133.007.064 (Box 64)
  - Media coverage reports and slides, 1996 -- 2005; UA133.007.040 (Box 40)
- Exhibitions and public programs records, circa 1960 -- 2016; UA133.008; 16.01 Linear Feet
  This series contains records from the Exhibitions and Public Programs office dating from circa 1967 to 2016. These records include exhibit files; exhibit slides and photographs; exhibit publicity materials including postcards, posters, programs, and calendars; and financial and long-range planning material. There are slides and photographs documenting the yearly 5th Year exhibition, the Traveling Scholars exhibitions, Alumni exhibitions, and the Annual Sale. Exhibition files contain planning documents including financial records, correspondence, and applications to exhibit which can include slides, photographs, and CDs or DVDs of artists' work.
  - Exhibition slides and promotional materials, circa 1960 -- 1999; UA133.008.027 (Box 27)
  - Art of the Alumni of the School of the Museum of Fine Arts, 1967; UA133.008.001.00005 (Box 1)
  - Art of the Alumni of the School of the Museum of Fine Arts, 1968; UA133.008.001.00006 (Box 1)
  - Centennial Celebration, 1970; UA133.008.001.00007 (Box 1)
  - Photographs, slides, exhibitions catalogs, and promotional material, circa 1970 -- 2016; UA133.008.007 (Box 7)
  - 5th Year Exhibition planning records, exhibition financial records, and art loan documentation, circa 1972 -- 2010; UA133.008.033 (Box 33)
  - 5th Year Exhibition and Traveling Scholar exhibition catalogs and promotional materials, circa 1977 -- 2014; UA133.008.008 (Box 8)
  - Transparencies, slides, and scroll, circa 1984 -- 1990; UA133.008.063 (Box 63)
  - Exhibition slides, 1984 -- 1992; UA133.008.030 (Box 30)
  - Traveling Scholar exhibition slides, and Alumni exhibition applications, circa 1987 -- 2006; UA133.008.044 (Box 44)
  - Publicity books, 1990 -- 1999; UA133.008.028 (Box 28)
  - Exhibition catalogs, circa 1990 -- 1999; UA133.008.010 (Box 10)
  - Exhibition CDs and DVDs, circa 1990 -- 2016; UA133.008.072 (Box 72)
  - MFA Thesis Exhibitions, Spring, 1994; UA133.008.001.00008 (Box 1)
  - Master of Fine Arts Thesis Exhibition, 1995; UA133.008.001.00009 (Box 1)
  - Master of Fine Arts Thesis Exhibition, 1995; UA133.008.001.00010 (Box 1)
  - Event calendars, awards, handbooks, and loans, circa 1997 -- 2007; UA133.008.067 (Box 67)
  - Art Sale records, circa 2000 -- 2010; UA133.008.031 (Box 31)
  - Exhibit planning and artist portfolios, circa 2003 -- 2013; UA133.008.029 (Box 29)
  - Traveling Scholar award and exhibition records, annual sale, and media coverage, circa 2003 -- 2016; UA133.008.032 (Box 32)
- Master of Fine Arts program records, 1979 -- 2014; UA133.009; 5.3 Linear Feet
  This series contains records from the Master of Fine Arts program dating from circa 1979 to 2014. These records include admissions materials; art sale files; graduate handbooks; MFA student rosters and grade sheets; Summer School program files; and teaching assistant records including rosters and training manuals. Admissions materials include interview and application files, and are closed for 75 years from date of creation.
  This series also contains graduate advising, faculty, curriculum, and colloquium files, as well as review board, critique, and student files. There are also student life records including awards, events, committees, funds and foundations, and registration files, and a small amount of slides of student work.
  - September 2016 accessions, circa 1979 -- 2011; UA133.009.001; 1.7 Linear Feet
    This sub-series contains admission files, photographs, publications, slides, student records, and Teaching Assistants files from the Master of Fine Arts program.
    - Admissions files, student records, and teaching assistants files, 1979 -- 1996; UA133.009.001.065 (Box 65)
    - Self-study committee documentation and reports, circa 1987 -- 1989; UA133.009.001.060 (Box 60)
    - Photographs, publications, slides, circa 1990 -- 2011; UA133.009.001.012 (Box 12)
  - 2018 accessions, 1989 -- 2014; UA133.009.002; 3.6 Linear Feet 3 record cartons
    This sub-series is arranged in order of accession.
    This sub-series contains admissions materials, including interview and application files; graduate advising, faculty, curriculum, and colloquium files; MFA rosters; graduate handbooks and drafts; review board, critique, and student files; art sale files; and files related to student life including awards, events, committees, funds and foundations, and registration files.
    - Admissions files and graduate advising, handbook, and curriculum files, 1989 -- 2013; UA133.009.002.444; 1.2 Linear Feet (Box 444)
      Transferred by the SMFA, 2018, accession UA-2019-020.
      Records containing information related to student education, staff and faculty employment, and Board of Trustees records are closed for 75 years from the date of creation. University records are closed for 20 years from the date of creation. Records older than 20 years that do not pertain to student education, staff and faculty employment and Board of Trustees records are open for research.
      This file contains admissions materials, including interview and application files; graduate advising and portfolio days files; MFA rosters; graduate handbooks and drafts; curriculum files; and academic progress files.
    - Graduate, student, and art sale files, 1998 -- 2014; UA133.009.002.445; 1.2 Linear Feet (Box 445)
      This file contains graduate faculty, curriculum, colloquium, and advising files; review board, critique, and student files; and art sale files.
    - Student files and student life files, 2000 -- 2014; UA133.009.002.446; 1.2 Linear Feet (Box 446)
      This file contains student review and critique files; and files related to student life including awards, events, committees, funds and foundations, and registration files.
- Office of the Provost records, circa 1980 -- 2016; UA133.010; 2.4 Linear Feet
  This series contains records of the Office of the Provost from 1980 to 2016. These records include syllabi; faculty curriculum vitae; strategic plans; and studies and reports, including a governance study, reports on a diversity initiative, and self-studies.
  University records are closed for 20 years from the date of creation. Records older than 20 years that do not pertain to student education, staff and faculty employment and Board of Trustees records are open for research. This series/sub-series may require review before it is available for use. Please contact DCA for further details.
  Received order has been maintained.
  - Diversity initiative, strategic plans, and self-study report, 1992 -- 2004; UA133.010.058 (Box 58)
  - Faculty curricula vitae, reports, self-studies, and syllabi, circa 1980 -- 2016; UA133.010.059 (Box 59)
- Audiovisual materials, 1980 -- 2016; UA133.011; 14.4 Linear Feet
  - Untitled, circa 1980 -- 2016; UA133.011.074.00001 (Box 74)
  - Video show 2000, UA133.011.074.00002 (Box 74)
    Hughs, Adrienne; Salandini, David; Spiegelman, Ben
  - Untitled, circa 1980 -- 2016; UA133.011.074.00003 (Box 74)
  - AIDS Awareness Day master, circa 1980 -- 2016; UA133.011.074.00004 (Box 74)
    Amalfitano, Lelia; Norton, Tom; Samour, Michelle
  - Untitled, circa 1980 -- 2016; UA133.011.074.00005 (Box 74)
  - Seventh annual Medal Awards dinner, 2002-05-21; UA133.011.074.00006 (Box 74)
    Close, Chuck
  - SMFA Commencement 2000, UA133.011.074.00007 (Box 74)
  - SMFA five year plan, 1998; UA133.011.074.00008 (Box 74)
  - Chisels and chainsaws Fox News spot, 2003-02-21; UA133.011.074.00009 (Box 74)
  - Stories, 2005; UA133.011.074.00010 (Box 74)
    Nakadate, Laurel
  - Please Excuse My Desire, 1996; UA133.011.074.00011 (Box 74)
    Swift, Chia-Hui
  - At a Distance, 2005; UA133.011.074.00012 (Box 74)
    Hicks, Jennifer
  - Seventh annual Medal Awards dinner, 2002-05-21; UA133.011.074.00013 (Box 74)
  - Medal Award 2001, 2001-01-01; UA133.011.074.00014 (Box 74)
  - Tribute to Bill Bagnall, circa 1980 -- 2016; UA133.011.074.00015 (Box 74)
    Bagnall, Bill
  - Doug and Mike Starn, circa 1980 -- 2016; UA133.011.074.00016 (Box 74)
    Starn, Doug; Starn, Mike
  - Salt - performance art project, 2005; UA133.011.074.00017 (Box 74)
    Lenzi, Kristina
  - Documentation, circa 1980 -- 2016; UA133.011.074.00018 (Box 74)
    LeBorious, M.
  - Four Painters Lecture Series, 1996-09-06; UA133.011.074.00019 (Box 74)
    Marcaccio, Fabian
  - Untitled, circa 1980 -- 2016; UA133.011.074.00020 (Box 74)
  - M. Q., circa 1980 -- 2016; UA133.011.074.00021 (Box 74)
  - Untitled, circa 1980 -- 2016; UA133.011.074.00022 (Box 74)
  - 16mm presentation - Pam, circa 1980 -- 2016; UA133.011.074.00023 (Box 74)
  - Untitled, circa 1980 -- 2016; UA133.011.074.00024 (Box 74)
  - Shellburne Thurber interview, 2001; UA133.011.074.00025 (Box 74)
    Thurber, Shellburne
  - Untitled, circa 1980 -- 2016; UA133.011.074.00026 (Box 74)
  - Colloquium 2, circa 1980 -- 2016; UA133.011.074.00027 (Box 74)
  - Untitled, circa 1980 -- 2016; UA133.011.074.00028 (Box 74)
  - Untitled, circa 1980 -- 2016; UA133.011.074.00029 (Box 74)
  - Untitled, circa 1980 -- 2016; UA133.011.074.00030 (Box 74)
  - Untitled, circa 1980 -- 2016; UA133.011.074.00031 (Box 74)
  - Rec tape, circa 1980 -- 2016; UA133.011.074.00032 (Box 74)
  - Untitled, circa 1980 -- 2016; UA133.011.074.00033 (Box 74)
  - Grad colloquium 2, circa 1980 -- 2016; UA133.011.074.00034 (Box 74)
  - Untitled, circa 1980 -- 2016; UA133.011.074.00035 (Box 74)
  - Untitled, circa 1980 -- 2016; UA133.011.074.00036 (Box 74)
  - Untitled, circa 1980 -- 2016; UA133.011.074.00037 (Box 74)
  - ARC interviews: Sue and Meg, circa 1980 -- 2016; UA133.011.074.00038 (Box 74)
  - Untitled, circa 1980 -- 2016; UA133.011.074.00039 (Box 74)
  - 42 attendees, circa 1980 -- 2016; UA133.011.074.00040 (Box 74)
  - Untitled, circa 1980 -- 2016; UA133.011.074.00041 (Box 74)
  - Creative Futures, 2012-02-17; UA133.011.074.00042 (Box 74)
    Charlton, Robert
  - Kristin Baker, circa 1980 -- 2016; UA133.011.074.00043 (Box 74)
    Baker, Kristin
  - Untitled, circa 1980 -- 2016; UA133.011.074.00044 (Box 74)
  - Untitled, circa 1980 -- 2016; UA133.011.074.00045 (Box 74)
  - Untitled, circa 1980 -- 2016; UA133.011.074.00046 (Box 74)
  - Minipolooza 1, 2009-07-24; UA133.011.074.00047 (Box 74)
  - Minipolooza 2, circa 2009 -- 2016; UA133.011.074.00048 (Box 74)
  - 48 attendees, circa 1980 -- 2016; UA133.011.074.00049 (Box 74)
  - Untitled, circa 1980 -- 2016; UA133.011.074.00050 (Box 74)
  - Lecture, circa 1980 -- 2016; UA133.011.074.00051 (Box 74)
  - Untitled, circa 1980 -- 2016; UA133.011.074.00052 (Box 74)
  - 8 photographs lecture, circa 1980 -- 2016; UA133.011.074.00053 (Box 74)
  - Untitled, circa 1980 -- 2016; UA133.011.074.00054 (Box 74)
  - Creative Futures, circa 1980 -- 2016; UA133.011.074.00055 (Box 74)
    Stanners, Michele
  - SMFA colloquium 2, 2006-11-20; UA133.011.074.00056 (Box 74)
  - Ataturk #1, circa 1980 -- 2016; UA133.011.074.00057 (Box 74)
  - Untitled, circa 1980 -- 2016; UA133.011.074.00058 (Box 74)
  - Untitled, circa 1980 -- 2016; UA133.011.074.00059 (Box 74)
  - Diana Punter, 2010-11-23; UA133.011.074.00060 (Box 74)
    Punter, Diana
  - SMFA colloquium 1, 2006-11-20; UA133.011.074.00061 (Box 74)
  - SMFA colloquium 3, 2006-11-20; UA133.011.074.00062 (Box 74)
  - Untitled, circa 1980 -- 2016; UA133.011.074.00063 (Box 74)
  - Melissa Levin interview, circa 1980 -- 2016; UA133.011.074.00064 (Box 74)
    Levin, Melissa
  - Untitled, circa 1980 -- 2016; UA133.011.074.00065 (Box 74)
  - Kristin Baker, circa 1980 -- 2016; UA133.011.074.00066 (Box 74)
  - SMFA colloquium 2, 2004-11-19; UA133.011.074.00067 (Box 74)
  - SMFA colloquium, 2004-11-18; UA133.011.074.00068 (Box 74)
  - The Melody, circa 1980 -- 2016; UA133.011.074.00069 (Box 74)
    Bentley, Tiffany
  - Karen tape 1, circa 1980 -- 2016; UA133.011.074.00070 (Box 74)
  - Anoka Faruqee, 2012-02-06; UA133.011.074.00071 (Box 74)
    Faruqee, Anoka
  - Untitled, circa 1980 -- 2016; UA133.011.074.00072 (Box 74)
  - Untitled, circa 1980 -- 2016; UA133.011.074.00073 (Box 74)
  - Cheyney Thompson, 2012-02-16; UA133.011.074.00074 (Box 74)
    Thompson, Cheyney
  - This one, circa 1980 -- 2016; UA133.011.074.00075 (Box 74)
  - Untitled, circa 1980 -- 2016; UA133.011.074.00076 (Box 74)
  - Untitled, circa 1980 -- 2016; UA133.011.074.00077 (Box 74)
  - Inside Out Info Session, circa 1980 -- 2016; UA133.011.074.00078 (Box 74)
  - Creative Futures 2, 2012-02-17; UA133.011.074.00079 (Box 74)
    Charlton, Rob
  - Untitled, circa 1980 -- 2016; UA133.011.074.00080 (Box 74)
  - Untitled, circa 1980 -- 2016; UA133.011.074.00081 (Box 74)
  - Untitled, circa 1980 -- 2016; UA133.011.074.00082 (Box 74)
  - Untitled, circa 1980 -- 2016; UA133.011.074.00083 (Box 74)
  - SMFA colloquium 3, 2004-11-19; UA133.011.074.00084 (Box 74)
  - SMFA 1 of 2, circa 1980 -- 2016; UA133.011.074.00085 (Box 74)
  - SMFA 2 of 2, circa 1980 -- 2016; UA133.011.074.00086 (Box 74)
  - Untitled, circa 1980 -- 2016; UA133.011.074.00087 (Box 74)
  - Johanna Bermudez Ruiz, circa 1980 -- 2016; UA133.011.074.00088 (Box 74)
    Bermudez Ruiz, Johanna
  - SMFA Riley Q&A, 2006-04-10; UA133.011.074.00089 (Box 74)
  - SMFA colloquium 4, 2006-11-20; UA133.011.074.00090 (Box 74)
  - SMFA Riley colloquium 1, 2006-04-10; UA133.011.074.00091 (Box 74)
  - SMFA Riley colloquium 2, 2006-04-10; UA133.011.074.00092 (Box 74)
  - SMFA Riley colloquium 3, 2006-04-10; UA133.011.074.00093 (Box 74)
  - Visiting Artist Lecture, 1988-03-01; UA133.011.076.00001 (Box 76)
    Schneemann, Carolee
  - Fresh Blood - A Dream Morphology, edit by J. Hudson 5/87, 1985-12-01; UA133.011.076.00002 (Box 76)
  - Fifth year documentation, 1989; UA133.011.076.00003 (Box 76)
  - Visiting Artist Lecture - Tape 2, 1988-08-08; UA133.011.076.00004 (Box 76)
    Cage, John
  - Robert Bly Workshop, 1988-03-05; UA133.011.076.00005 (Box 76)
    Bly, Robert
  - Visiting Artist Lecture - Part 4, 1988; UA133.011.076.00006 (Box 76)
  - Levni Yilmaz, 1994; UA133.011.076.00007 (Box 76)
    Yilmaz, Levni
  - Visiting Artist Lecture, 1988-02-22; UA133.011.076.00008 (Box 76)
  - Visiting Artist Lecture - Part 2, 1988; UA133.011.076.00009 (Box 76)
    Wilson, Robert Forrest, 1883-1942.
  - Schneemann lecture 2, 1988; UA133.011.076.00010 (Box 76)
  - Video dub 2, 1994; UA133.011.076.00011 (Box 76)
  - Tape 1, circa 1980 -- 2016; UA133.011.076.00012 (Box 76)
  - Stardumb, 1993; UA133.011.076.00013 (Box 76)
    Keough, Colleen
  - Visiting Artist Lecture, 1988-08-08; UA133.011.076.00014 (Box 76)
    Truitt, Anne
  - Video dub 1, circa 1980 -- 2016; UA133.011.076.00015 (Box 76)
  - Four Sculptors Lecture Series, 2002-09-16; UA133.011.076.00016 (Box 76)
    Sienna, James
  - Four Painters Lecture Series, 2002-10-07; UA133.011.076.00017 (Box 76)
    Ruyter, Lisa
  - In Conversation, 2002-10-09; UA133.011.076.00018 (Box 76)
    Koons, Jeff
  - Katy Shimert, 2001-01-01; UA133.011.076.00019 (Box 76)
    Shimert, Katy
  - Four Painters Lecture Series, 2002-10-01; UA133.011.076.00020 (Box 76)
    Risley, Jack
  - In Conversation, 2002-09-23; UA133.011.076.00021 (Box 76)
    Ramos, Sandra
  - Visiting Artist Lecture Series - Sculptor and Critic, 2001-11-06; UA133.011.076.00022 (Box 76)
    Scanlan, Joe
  - Visiting Artist Lecture Series, 2001-11-06; UA133.011.076.00023 (Box 76)
    Ramirez Jonas, Paul
  - Grooming a More Masculine You, 2000-01-01; UA133.011.076.00024 (Box 76)
    Lynelt, Randy
  - Beckwith Lecture - Woman As Protagonist: The Art of Nan. Spero, 2001-10-29; UA133.011.076.00025 (Box 76)
    Spero, Nancy
  - Visiting Artist Lecture Series, 2001-10-24; UA133.011.076.00026 (Box 76)
    Coe, Sue
  - Four Painters Lecture Series, 2002-09-30; UA133.011.077.00001 (Box 77)
    Ali, Laylah
  - Beckwith Lecture - "It is Difficult" (Tape 1), 2002-10-21; UA133.011.077.00002 (Box 77)
    Jaar, Alfredo
  - Beckwith Lecture - "It is Difficult" (Tape 2), 2002-10-21; UA133.011.077.00003 (Box 77)
  - Panel Discussion, 2002-10-28; UA133.011.077.00004 (Box 77)
    Rubenstein, Barnet
  - Four Sculptors Lecture Series, 2002-10-29; UA133.011.077.00005 (Box 77)
    Joo, Michael
  - Visiting Artist Lecture - Part 2, 1988; UA133.011.077.00006 (Box 77)
  - Video Exhibition - Single Channel Video, 2000; UA133.011.077.00007 (Box 77)
  - Annual tape 2, circa 1980 -- 2016; UA133.011.077.00008 (Box 77)
  - 5th Year 1992 (raw footage), 1992-01-01; UA133.011.077.00009 (Box 77)
  - Visiting Artist Lecture - Part 1, 1988; UA133.011.077.00010 (Box 77)
  - Untitled, circa 1980 -- 2016; UA133.011.077.00011 (Box 77)
  - Visiting Artist Lecture - Part 3, 1988; UA133.011.077.00012 (Box 77)
  - Visiting Artist Lecture - Tape 1, 1988-08-08; UA133.011.077.00013 (Box 77)
  - Projection video exhibition, 2000; UA133.011.077.00014 (Box 77)
  - Visiting Artist Lecture - Part 3, 1988; UA133.011.077.00015 (Box 77)
  - Visiting Artist Lecture, 1988; UA133.011.077.00016 (Box 77)
  - Visiting Artist Lecture, 1988; UA133.011.077.00017 (Box 77)
  - Visiting Artist Lecture Series, 2002-01-23; UA133.011.078.00001 (Box 78)
    Gaither, Barry
  - Visiting Artist Lecture Series - Installation Artist, 2002-01-22; UA133.011.078.00002 (Box 78)
    Fernandez, Teresita
  - Jeanne Silverthorne, 2001-01-01; UA133.011.078.00003 (Box 78)
    Silverthorne, Jeanne
  - Medal Award 2001, UA133.011.078.00004 (Box 78)
  - The Revival Church of the Living Womb, 2002-01-29; UA133.011.078.00005 (Box 78)
    Heavy Hit'az
  - Nayland Blake, 2001; UA133.011.078.00006 (Box 78)
    Blake, Nayland
  - Student Annual 2002 - Single Channel, 2002-01-01; UA133.011.078.00007 (Box 78)
  - Painting wasn't Ladylike: Women Artist at SMFA 1870-1940, 2001-10-10; UA133.011.078.00008 (Box 78)
    Hirshler, Erica
  - Gallery Talk, 2001-10-12; UA133.011.078.00009 (Box 78)
    Petlin, Irving
  - Visiting Artist Lecture, 2001-02-01; UA133.011.078.00010 (Box 78)
    Dunning, Jeanne
  - Paradise Under Reconstruction in the Aesthetic of Funk, 2001-02-22; UA133.011.078.00011 (Box 78)
  - Four Sculptors Lecture Series, 2002-09-10; UA133.011.078.00012 (Box 78)
    McCaslin, Matthew
  - Deborah Bright, 2001-01-01; UA133.011.078.00013 (Box 78)
    Bright, Deborah
  - Eight Sculptors Lecture Series, 2001-01-30; UA133.011.078.00014 (Box 78)
    Edmier, Keith
  - Sound Panel, 2001; UA133.011.078.00015 (Box 78)
  - Visiting Artist Lecture Series - Installation Artist, 2002-02-12; UA133.011.078.00016 (Box 78)
    Apfelbaum, Polly
  - Visiting Artist Lecture Series, 2001-10-23; UA133.011.078.00017 (Box 78)
    Bolande, Jennifer
  - Dangerous Guitars, 2001-01-01; UA133.011.078.00018 (Box 78)
    Kuronen, Darcy
  - Visiting Artist Lecture Series, 2002-02-12; UA133.011.078.00019 (Box 78)
    Hyde, James
  - Visiting Artist Lecture, 2001-01-22; UA133.011.078.00020 (Box 78)
    Robbins, David
  - Judge's Panel Tape for Student Annual Exhibition, 2001-03-03; UA133.011.078.00021 (Box 78)
  - Faculty Lecture Series, 2000-01-24; UA133.011.078.00022 (Box 78)
    Harries, Mags
  - Visiting Artist Lecture Series, 2001-10-02; UA133.011.078.00023 (Box 78)
    Hauft, Amy
  - Four Sculptors Lecture Series, 2001-01-21; UA133.011.078.00024 (Box 78)
    Leone, Christopher
  - Student Award - Single Channel #2 Looped, 2002; UA133.011.078.00025 (Box 78)
  - Four Painters Lecture Series, 2000-02-04; UA133.011.078.00026 (Box 78)
    Kami, Y. Z.
  - Faculty Lecture Series, 2000-04-14; UA133.011.078.00027 (Box 78)
    Gamboa, Harry
  - Video Panel, 2000; UA133.011.078.00028 (Box 78)
  - Faculty Lecture Series, 2000-01-01; UA133.011.078.00029 (Box 78)
    Janowitz, Joel
  - Four Sculptors Lecture Series, 2000-01-03; UA133.011.078.00030 (Box 78)
    Lesko, Lauren
  - Faculty Lecture Series, 2000-01-02; UA133.011.078.00031 (Box 78)
    Barreres, Domingo
  - Four Painters Lecture Series, 1999-10-08; UA133.011.078.00032 (Box 78)
    Cronin, Patricia
  - Faculty Lecture Series, 1999-10-05; UA133.011.078.00033 (Box 78)
    Kauper, Kurt
  - Maria Magdalena Campos-Pons, 1999-10-12; UA133.011.078.00034 (Box 78)
    Campos-Pons, Maria Magdalena
  - Faculty Lecture Series, 1999-11-02; UA133.011.078.00035 (Box 78)
    Chavoya, Ondine
  - Frieda Lee Mock, 1999-09-21; UA133.011.078.00036 (Box 78)
    Mock, Frieda Lee
  - Four Sculptors Lecture Series, 1999-11-04; UA133.011.078.00037 (Box 78)
    Hsu-Flanders, Lillian
  - Visiting Artist Lecture, 1999-10-25; UA133.011.078.00038 (Box 78)
    Rubenstein, Bradley
  - Mary Ellen Strom, 1999-10-26; UA133.011.078.00039 (Box 78)
    Strom, Mary Ellen
  - Otis Tamasakaus, 1999-10-22; UA133.011.078.00040 (Box 78)
    Tamasakaus, Otis
  - Nicole Eisenman, 1999-10-13; UA133.011.078.00041 (Box 78)
    Eisenman, Nicole
  - Beckwith Lecture, 1999-10-20; UA133.011.078.00042 (Box 78)
  - Faculty Lecture Series, 2000-01-26; UA133.011.078.00043 (Box 78)
    Daborn, Erica
  - Power Play's Panel, 2000-02-01; UA133.011.078.00044 (Box 78)
    Marclay, Christian; Sharp, Elliot; Mori, Ikue
  - Faculty Lecture Series, 2000-01-25; UA133.011.078.00045 (Box 78)
    Bergstein, Gerry
  - Four Sculptors Lecture Series, 1999-10-07; UA133.011.078.00046 (Box 78)
    Dalton, Jennifer
  - Faculty Lecture Series, 2000-04-14; UA133.011.078.00047 (Box 78)
  - Faculty Lecture Series, 2000-02-14; UA133.011.078.00048 (Box 78)
    Madden, Peter
  - Faculty Lecture Series, 2000-02-18; UA133.011.078.00049 (Box 78)
    Davison, David
  - Four Painters Lecture Series, 2001-10-11; UA133.011.078.00050 (Box 78)
    Costa, Eduardo
  - J. C. Herwood, 2001-01-01; UA133.011.078.00051 (Box 78)
    Herwood, J. C.
  - Sound Show Lecture, 2001-01-01; UA133.011.078.00052 (Box 78)
  - Yuri Norstein - part 1, 2001-01-01; UA133.011.078.00053 (Box 78)
    Norstein, Yuri
  - Yuri Norstein - part 2, 2001-01-01; UA133.011.078.00054 (Box 78)
  - Four Sculptors Lecture Series, 1984-10-05; UA133.011.080.00001 (Box 80)
    Bowen, Nancy
  - Eight Photographers, 2008-11-13; UA133.011.080.00002 (Box 80)
    Davis, Tim
  - Liz Choen, 2008-10-09; UA133.011.080.00003 (Box 80)
    Choen, Liz
  - Four Painters Lecture Series, 2008-03-04; UA133.011.080.00004 (Box 80)
    Deroubaix, Damien
  - Joan Jonas, 2008-03-05; UA133.011.080.00005 (Box 80)
    Jonas, Joan
  - SMFA feminism panel - tape 1 of 4, 2008-03-07; UA133.011.080.00006 (Box 80)
  - SMFA feminism panel - tape 2 of 4, 2008-03-07; UA133.011.080.00007 (Box 80)
  - SMFA feminism panel - tape 3 of 4, 2008-03-07; UA133.011.080.00008 (Box 80)
  - SMFA feminism panel - tape 4 of 4, 2008-03-07; UA133.011.080.00009 (Box 80)
  - Four Sculptors Lecture Series, 2008-03-11; UA133.011.080.00010 (Box 80)
    Hassenfeld, Kristen
  - Courtney Smith, 2008-11-04; UA133.011.080.00011 (Box 80)
    Smith, Courtney
  - Hilary Harkness, 2008-10-14; UA133.011.080.00012 (Box 80)
    Harkness, Hilary
  - Michelle Lopez, 2008-10-21; UA133.011.080.00013 (Box 80)
    Lopez, Michelle
  - Valerie Hegarty, 2008-10-28; UA133.011.080.00014 (Box 80)
    Hegarty, Valerie
  - Chris Martin, 2008-09-30; UA133.011.080.00015 (Box 80)
    Martin, Chris
  - Four Photographers Lecture Series, 2008-03-18; UA133.011.080.00016 (Box 80)
    Sanguinetti, Alessandro
  - Chris Doyle, 2008-11-18; UA133.011.080.00017 (Box 80)
    Doyle, Chris
  - Inka Essenhigh, 2008-11-25; UA133.011.080.00018 (Box 80)